now it's time to play scare BNB scare
BNB Airbnb is a fantastic resource for
people who want all the discomfort of
not staying in a hotel combined with all
the fear of sleeping near
strangers people list their actual homes
and then people they don't know come
stay there it's sort of like Goldilocks
with PayPal uh so I'm going to show you
a picture from an Airbnb listing and I
would like you guys to give me a line
from your review after having stayed
there all right here's the first one
this Co chairs the ground with a fox
named rabies and some creepy art
installations what was that stay like
Natasha hard to when ominous
children's laughter begins at
[Laughter]
midnight next one the this one's in Soul
and it looks like a prison
camp yes Natasha uh easily the nicest
shoe rack I've ever slept in
also wait also I heart the smell of
kimchi
farts F no this was fine but the maids
wore white lab coats and the free
breakfast was at the end of a
maze points it's for
science all right next one This creepy
room rented by this not at all
creepy got you
pregnant
Mark uh reasonable rates but I got tired
of putting the lotion in the
[Laughter]
basket he calls it a detach Shack
toe it's clever the room is very
spacious which is nice because the
smiling lunatic never leaves the
room he just sits on the whole time
watch out with you you want me to wake
you up at time you can't the other part
of that picture is like his half of the
bed that he's got cut
off it looks like a small bed but that's
literally where he used had a great stay
until my unborn child was ripped from my
womb as I
slept close to Subway points
okay